http://www.fsplanet.com/privacy.htm

Cookies
Our Site uses cookies for other purposes.
Advertisers
We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.
Some customer data is shared with the advertising companies.
Contests
We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like email address).
Contact information from the contests is used for other purposes.
External Links
This site contains links to other sites. FSPLANET.COM is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Public Forums
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
Children’s Guidelines
We care about children and understand that they have special privacy needs. Therefore, we have adopted the following privacy policy regarding children:
We will NOT collect, use, or distribute to third parties personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent.
We will NOT give the child access to unmonitored chat rooms, message boards, email accounts, or other services that would give the child the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent
When verifiable parental consent is not obtained, we will only use the online contact information (such as email) to:
Respond directly to the child’s request on a one-time basis and not use that information to re-contact the child for other purposes.
Request the name or online contact information of a parent for the purpose of obtaining verifiable parental consent or providing parental notification.
Respond more than once directly to a specific request from a child (such as in the case where a child requests a newsletter subscription) and not used to re-contact the child for other purposes. We will use our best efforts to provide parental notification, which will include the nature and intended use as well as an opportunity for the parent to prevent the use of the information and participation in the activity.
We will NOT entice the child to divulge more information than is needed to participate in any activity, game, or service.
We will provide the parent a description of the specific types of a personally identifiable information collected from their child upon request. We will allow the parent to refuse further use or future online collection of personally identifiable information and provide a way for a parent to obtain any personally identifiable information collected from their child.
We will provide notice to children in age appropriate terms of what personally identifiable information is to be collected.
We will NOT provide any links to Web sites that are unsuitable for children.
We will encourage children to get their parent’s permission before sharing personal information online.
As freeware is permitted to distribute archives subject to the following conditions
– The archive must be distributed without modification to the contents of the archive. Redistributing this archive with any files added, removed or modified is prohibited.
– The inclusion of any individual file from this archive in another archive without the prior permission of the author is prohibited.
– No charge may be made for this archive other than that to cover the cost of its distribution. If a fee is charged it must be made clear to the purchaser that the archive is freeware and that the fee is to cover the distributor’s costs of providing the archive.
– The authors’ rights and wishes concerning archives must be respected.
– Permission for distribution is not required since the content is being distributed as freeware. Permission is required when any part of the content is going to be included in a commercial product.
Search
RSSGet updates
Google PlusJoin our circle
TwitterFollow us
FacebookBecome our fan
Popular
Latest
Comments
Flight1 and Dreamfleet: BOEING 727 “WHISPERJET”
FS98/FS2000 A-10 Warthog “Flying Tigers”
FS2000 Jolly Rogers Grumman F-14A Tomcat v1.1
FLIGHTSIM 2000 Specific – LOCKHEED SR-71A “Blackbird”
FS2000 scenery — U.S.S. Saratoga CV60
FS2000 North American F-86K & panel
737 PILOT IN COMMAND
Battle of Britain II Wings of Victory
Beech D17 "Staggerwing"
FS2004 North American SNJ-5 NAS GLENVIEW (1956)
Operations Manual?
FS98/FS2000 A-10 Warthog “Flying Tigers”
FS2000 Jolly Rogers Grumman F-14A Tomcat v1.1
FLIGHTSIM 2000 Specific – LOCKHEED SR-71A “Blackbird”
Beech D17 "Staggerwing"
FS2004 North American SNJ-5 NAS GLENVIEW (1956)
Operations Manual?
© 2020 Download – FSPLANET – Top Quality Flight Sims since 1997. All rights reserved.
